http://www.accuform.com/legal/accuform-privacy-policy

Shop By Categoryadd
Petrochemical Express Welding Express Construction Express The Simpsons™ Safety Signs Safety Labels Safety Scoreboards Safety Tags Pipe Markers ID Tags 5S Workplace Organization Lockout Tagout Devices Confined Space Identification GHS HazCom Shipping Labels & Placards Traffic Signs Traffic Control Barriers & Barricades Floor Signs & Tapes Specialty Marking Safety Recognition & Event Supplies Safety Banners & Posters Custom Products
Custom Productsadd
OSHA & ANSI Safety Signs Bilingual Safety Signs No Header Signs Custom Header Signs Custom SiteTags® Custom Safety Tags Custom NFPA Placards Custom Street Signs Hard Hat Labels Custom Floor Signs Custom Stencils Custom Arc Flash Signs Reserved Parking Drive Safely Sign VPP Banners
COVID-19 Productsadd
Social Distancing Hygiene Floor Markers Safety Barriers
Articles & Infoadd
News Articles Press Releases Virtual Catalog Digi-Day® Information & Reference Product Literature Tool Box Accuform Videos
Quotes & Ordersadd
Cart Order From Quote Register Distributor Login Log In Log Out
Contactadd
Contact Accuform Request a Catalog Frequently Asked Questions Accuform's W-9 Form Current Job Listings
Accountadd
Reset Password Log In Register Log Out
Home > News > Accuform Privacy Policy
Accuform.com Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Accuform collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.accuform.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Accuform.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationAccuform may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:To improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.To process paymentsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.Third party websitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.Changes to this privacy policyAccuform has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Accuformwww.accuform.com 16228 Flight Path DriveBrooksville, FL 34604, United States1.800.237.1001customerservice@accuform.comThis document was last updated on January 1, 2014.
Your Account Manager
Mark MacGregor
Inside Sales Representative
mmacgregor@accuform.com
(800) 237-1001
Text Us
Send Email
Join Our Mailing List
Subscribe
Follow Accuform
Join Our Mailing List
Subscribe
Proud Members
All Contents Copyright © 2020 Accuform Safely Made in the USA.®
Petrochemical Express
Welding Express
Construction Express
The Simpsons™
Safety Signs
Safety Labels
Safety Scoreboards
Safety Tags
Safety Banners & Posters
OSHA & ANSI Safety Signs Don't settle for just any old sign when it comes to workplace safety and compliance. Create a custom OSHA & ANSI safety sign with the exact message you need, when you need it.
Get Started
Bilingual Safety Signs Ensure all workers understand the safety messages posted around your jobsite or inside the workplace with custom bilingual safety signs. Customize your message here!
Get Started
No Header Signs Need something a little different and don't want to meet specific regulations? Make a statement with your own customized no header signs. Create a unique sign and message here!
Get Started
Custom Header Signs Make your safety message your own - don't blend in, stand out! Grab the attention of your workers with custom header signs. Easily create the exact sign you need right here!
Get Started
Custom SiteTags® Making Site Tags™ has never been easier with our custom predesigned site tag builder! Simply upload your worker's image, name, and department, and select material and quantity.
Get Started
Custom Builders
Custom Safety Tags
Custom NFPA Placards
Custom Street Signs
Hard Hat Labels
Custom Floor Signs Custom Stencils
Custom Arc Flash Signs
Reserved Parking Drive Safely Sign VPP Banners
COVID-19 Products With millions of positive coronavirus cases in America, this pandemic continues to change the world as we know it. New challenges to not only keep businesses, workers, customers, and the public safe but also to reduce the impact of COVID-19 are continuous reminders that we all have a significant role in preventing the spread of this virus.
To help your business, we created 800+ COVID-19 safety identification solutions. Learn More
Social Distancing Social distancing also called “physical distancing,” means keeping space between yourself and other people outside of your home. Remind others to stand 6 feet apart with social and physical distancing signs at work stations, production facilities, checkout aisles, grocery stores, restaurants, and more.
Read More
Hygiene Practicing hand hygiene is a simple yet effective way to prevent infections. Cleaning your hands can prevent the spread of germs, including those resistant to antibiotics, and are becoming difficult, if not impossible, to treat. Avoid the spread of germs by promoting proper hand hygiene in your business.
Read More
Floor Markers Effectively promote social distancing in your workplace to stop the spread of the coronavirus with floor marking messages. Alert others to stop at a safe distance and maintain 6 feet of space between each other when waiting for products or services.
Read More
Safety Barriers Prevent face-to-face interactions at close workstations in industrial, office, and commercial settings. Conveniently move around free-standing safety barriers with ease to any desired location and do your part to stop the spread.
Read More
6 New Dangers That Winter Weather Brings to the Workplace
Winter brings a heavy dose of new dangers to deal with every day for those who work outside. But it doesn’t stop there. Even inside workplaces can have added hazards due to Jack Frost’s foul tempe...
Read More
Your Safety Signs Will Be More Effective When You
You have a lot of safety signs. You take pride in staying up to code and taking your employees’ safety seriously. But are your signs doing as much good as you think? Are you utilizing your floors to...
Read More
These 5 Dangerous Workplace Scenarios Can Be Avoid
As an employer, you have many responsibilities. But the most essential task is protecting the health and safety of those in your workplace. Safety is the number one priority - and an effective LOTO pr...
Read More
News Archive Press Releases Virtual Catalog Accuform Videos Digi-Day® Information & Reference Product Literature Tool Box
Cart
Order From Quote
Register
Distributor Login
Log In
Log Out
Contact Accuform
Request a Catalog
Log Out
Barriers & BarricadesConfined Space Custom Vehicle SignsConstructionContainer Tags & LabelsFloor SignsHaz-com/GHS Safety LabelsLED Sign ProjectorLockout/Tagout & Security DevicesPipe MarkersSafety Banners & PostersSafety LabelsSafety ScoreboardsSafety SignsSafety TagsShipping Labels & PlacardsSmall Vehicle LabelsSpecialty MarkingTough-Mark™ Heavy-Duty Floor MarkiTraffic ControlTraffic SignsDigital SignageTruck & Driver LabelsTruck & Trailer LabelsVehicle Labels
Welding Fold-UpsWelding Gas Cylinder Lockout CapWelding Gauge Marking StickersWelding Safety LabelsWelding Safety Poster FrameWelding Safety PostersWelding Safety SignsWelding Safety Tag HoldersWelding Safety TagsWelding Safety Welding BannersWelding Safety Welding KitsWelding ScreensWelding Status Alert Flip-Plac™ Sign
Construction BannersConstruction Contractor Preferred SignsConstruction Hard Hat StickersConstruction HazCom & GHSConstruction LabelsConstruction Lockout TagoutConstruction Parking PermitsConstruction Posts & ChainConstruction PPE ChartsConstruction Safety ScoreboardsConstruction Safety TagsConstruction Site PostersConstruction TapesConstruction Traffic ControlConstruction Traffic SignsConstruction Welding ScreensContractor Preferred Corrugated Plastic Signs
Decibel SignsDigital ScoreboardsFloor SignsHeat Stress Digital SignsWelding Screen
5S Red Tag AreaANSI SignsChemical SignsConstruction SignsCSA SignsCustom SignsDecibel Meter SignsDirection SignsDoor SignsElectrical SignsEmergency SignsEmployee SignsEntrance SignsEquipment SignsExit SignsFire Safety SignsFirst Aid SignsFrench Only SignsGate SignsHazmat SignsHousekeeping SignsHygiene SignsInfectious DiseaseMotivational SignsOSHA Safety Equipment SignsOSHA SignsPersonal Protection SignsPublic HealthRestriction SignsRestroom SignsSafety Slogan SignsSign AccessoriesSmoking SignsSpanish Only SignsSpecialty SignsSpecific Hazard SignsTraffic Industrial SignsVisitor Signs
ANSI LabelsChemical LabelsConstruction LabelsCSA LabelsCustom LabelsDirection LabelsDoor LabelsElectrical LabelsEmergency LabelsEmployee LabelsEntrance LabelsEquipment LabelsExit LabelsFire Safety LabelsFirst Aid LabelsFrench Only LabelsFunny StickersHazardous Waste LabelsHazmat LabelsHousekeeping LabelsHygiene LabelsOSHA LabelsPersonal Protection LabelsRestriction LabelsSafety Incentive LabelsSmoking LabelsSpanish Only LabelsSpecialty LabelsSpecific Hazards LabelsTraffic Industrial LabelsVisitor Labels
Custom ScoreboardsDigital ScoreboardsTemperatureManual Tracking ScoreboardsTemperature Display
Blank TagsBox of TagsConfined Space TagsCustom TagsGeneral Safety TagsHazmat TagsInspection TagsLockout TagsPerforated Tags By-The-RollProduction Control TagsRepair TagsSpecialty TagsStatus Alert TagsStatus Record TagsTag AccessoriesTag CentersTag TiesTags By-The-RollTags By-The-Roll With Grommets
Accu-Detect Metal-Detectable Pipe MarkersCustom Pipe MarkersIIAR Ammonia Pipe MarkersIIAR Component MarkersPipe Marker AccessoriesRoll Form Pipe MarkersRoll Tape Pipe MarkersSpecialty Pipe MarkersStock Pipe Markers
Energy Source ID TagsID Tag AccessoriesMetal ID TagsPlastic ID Tags
5S & 6S Banners & Posters5S Electronic Scoreboards5S Floor Marking5S Floor Signs5S ReferenceGauge MarkingHoldersInsertsInventory Marking DotsLabel DispensersLabel PrintingLetters & NumbersPegboards & HardwarePPE DispensersPPE IdentificationQuality Control ProductsRed Tag SuppliesShadow-WrapSite-BoardsStore-BoardsStore-DrawersTPM SuppliesVinyl Shadows
Cable LockoutsChain LockoutsCircuit Breaker LockoutsEnergy Source IdentificationHaspsLock BoxesLockout Center BoardsLockout DocumentationLockout KitsLockout TrainingPadlocksPlug LockoutsSecurity SealsSwitch LockoutsValve LockoutsWorksite Lockouts
Confined Space BarriersConfined Space Fold-Ups®Confined Space LabelsConfined Space PermitsConfined Space SignsConfined Space Stencils
GHS LabelsGHS PostersGHS SignsGHS TrainingGHS Wallet CardsSDS BindersSDS Centers
Emergency HornsHazard Communication LabelsHazard Communication PostersHazard Communication SignsHazCom TrainingHMCIS LabelsHMCIS SignsHMCIS Wallet GuidesNFPA LabelsNFPA PlacardsNFPA Wallet GuidesSharp Containers
Shipping AccessoriesShipping LabelsShipping PlacardsFence Wrap Mesh BannersTransport Markings
Bicycle SignsBlinker SignsCrossing SignsCustom Traffic SignsDriver Safety SignsFacility Traffic SignsFluorescent Yellow-Green SignsGeneral Service SignsIntersection SignsLane Control SignsParking SignsPedestrian SignsRailroad SignsRecycle-Grade Traffic SignsRoad Condition SignsSpeed Limit SignsStop SignsSupplemental Traffic SignsTemporary Traffic ControlTraffic BeaconsTraffic Direction SignsTraffic MarkersTraffic Sign AccessoriesTruck Restriction SignsYield Signs
Gate Arm BarriersHigh Visibility ApparelMarker StakesMirror GuardsPaddle SignsTraffic BarrelsTraffic BarricadesTraffic Cone AccessoriesTraffic ConesTraffic FlagsTraffic LightingTraffic MirrorsWindsocks
Banner BarriersBarricade TapeBarricade WrapBollardsBumpersExpandable BarricadesFold-Up X-Barricade SignsQuickFold™ Barricade SystemRope SignsSafety ChainStanchionsTemporary FenceWelding Screens
Floor SignsFloor TapesLED Sign ProjectorsPavement SignsPortable Floor SignsSafety Cones
Embossed Aluminum CharactersFloor StencilsGeneral StencilsLetters & NumbersLot MarkingParking PermitsSafety StencilsSpecialty Marking PaintsUtility Line-Marking LabelsUtility Marking
Badge HoldersCountry & State FlagsEvent SuppliesLanyardsPortable Banner StandsSafety Meeting KitsSafety Motivational FlagsSafety PatchesSafety PinsSuggestion Boxes
Custom BannersCustom PostersMotivational MatsSafety BannersSafety Motivation SetsSafety PostersWall GraphicsWindow Graphics
